Mss.B.F327
American Philosophical Society
- Rev. Calvin Whiting to Rev. Jonathan Newell, 1793 September 10; No. 2312
- Rev. Calvin Whiting to Rev. Jonathan Newell, 1794 May 20; No. 2313
- James Williams to Justin Ely, 1780?; No. 2314
- Jack Rathbone (Dr. Joshua Ebenezer Rathbone Birch) to Peter DeWitt, 1801 June 16; No. 2315
- Levin Winder to James McHenry, 1796 October 29; No. 2316
- William Woodford to George Washington, 1778 September 12; No. 2317
- Thomas Woolford, 1781 June 26; No. 2318
- Thomas Woolford to James Woolford, 1780 August 24; No. 2319
- William Woolford to James Woolford, 1780 August 10; No. 2320
- William Woolford to James Woolford, 1781 April 21; No. 2321
- Dr. Thomas Young to the Committee of Coorespondence of the Sons of Liberty, 1766 April 21; No. 2322
- R______ Washington to his uncle, 1893 February 7; No. 2323
- John Amiel, 1782 March 31; No. 2324
- John Armstrong to Charles Lee, 1776 August 3; No. 2325
- John Armstrong, Jr. to Jonathan Bull, 1814 July 30; No. 2326
- Josiah Bartlett to William Whipple, 1776 August 27; No. 2327
- Clement Biddle to John Shaw, 1776 September 11; No. 2328
- Clement Biddle to William Lowrey, 1778 December 30; No. 2329
- Clement Biddle to George Washington, 1780 May 28; No. 2330
- Elias Boudinot to Joshua "Messereau" Mersereau, 1777 August 19; No. 2331
- Elias Boudinot to Elisha Boudinot, 1800 January 13; No. 2332
- John Broome, by order of the Chamber the New York Chamber of Commerce to the New York Legislature, n.d.; No. 2333
- Aaron Burr to Nathaniel Lawrence, 1789 May 26; No. 2334
- Gideon Burt, 1775 October 21; No. 2335
- Sir Guy Carleton, Thomas Anguish and George Drummond to Richard Rigby, 1781 December 12; No. 2336
- Charles Carroll of Carrollton to the Committee of Arrangement, 1829 July 3; No. 2337
- Francis Rush Clark, 1776-1779; No. 2338; 2.0 vols.
- George Clinton to Jonathan Burrall, 1798 April 6; No. 2339
- Sir Henry Clinton, Jr. to James Ogilvie, 1815 September 14; No. 2340
- David Cobb to Henry Jackson, 1780 March 22; No. 2341
- State of Connecticut, Comptroller's Office, 1790 March 5; No. 2342
- State of Connecticut, Pay-Table Office to John Lawrence, 1782 November 22; No. 2343
- State of Connecticut, Pay-Table Office to John Lawrence, 1783 January 8; No. 2344
- George Washington Parke Custis to Miss ______ Pleasanton, 1854 July 26; No. 2345
- Henry Dearborn to Callender Irvine, 1812 July 11; No. 2346
- David Dexter, 1778 October; No. 2347
- William Ellis, 1780 May 26; No. 2348
- Dr. Thomas Ewing to the Provincial Congress of New Jersey, 1776 February 6; No. 2349
- Lord Thomas Fairfax to Daniel French, Sr., 1741 March 4; No. 2350
- Timothy Fay to the Committee of Pay-Table, 1781 March 12; No. 2351
- Benjamin Franklin to David Rittenhouse, 1786 May 15; No. 2352
- Frederick Frelinghuysen to William Livingston, 1781 July 20; No. 2353
- Society of Friends, 1776-1779; No. 2354
- Horatio Gates to Charles Townshend, 1766 April 3; No. 2355
- Horatio Gates to Dwight Foster, n.d.; No. 2356
- Ebenezer Gay to Edward? Rogers, 1779 July 29; No. 2357
- Jeremiah Gilman, 1776 May; No. 2358
- Great Britain, King George III to William Speke, 1798 May 31; No. 2359
- Nathanael Greene to John Townes, 1781 May 24; No. 2360
- Nathanael Greene to Mordecai Gist, 1783 May 20; No. 2361
- Roger Gregory to Augustine Washington, 1726 May 17; No. 2362
- John Haas, Johannes "Magno" Mayer, and Peter Colsher to William Franklin and the Council and General Assembly of New Jersey, 1768 April 15; No. 2363
- Alexander Hamilton to John McComb, Jr., 1791 June 8; No. 2364
- Alexander Hamilton to James McHenry, 1799 July 10; No. 2365
- Alexander Hamilton to Nehemiah Freeman, 1799 September; No. 2366
- John Hancock to William Burbeck, 1782 August 17; No. 2367
- Josiah Harmar, 1780 May 2; No. 2368
- William Heath to George Clinton, 1782 June 24; No. 2369
- James Hillhouse to Samuel Huntington, 1793 March 2; No. 2370
- Benjamin Howard to the Treasurer of Maryland, 1780 July 28; No. 2371
- John Eager Howard to Philip Nicklin and Robert E. Griffith, 1802 December 4; No. 2372
- John Jay, 1796 March 18; No. 2373
- Thomas Jefferson, 1776, 1784-1794; No. 2374
- Thomas Jefferson to Richard Richardson, 1800 February 17; No. 2375
- Thomas Jefferson to Thomas Leiper, 1815 June 12, 14; No. 2376; Discusses at length the government of Britain and [Napoleon] Bonaparte and remarks: "the less we have to do with the amities or enmities of Europe, the better. Not in our day, but at no distant one, we may shake a rod over the heads of all"; comments on misrepresentations of Jefferson's opinions by the Federalists and expresses confidence in President [James] Madison's conduct of the war with Britain, but expresses hope for peace; postscript: informs him that Jefferson just received news that the allied powers in Europe declared Louis XVIII ruler of France instead of Napoleon, and wishes the latter
  David Library Item Number: 2376; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Rufus King to James Sheaf, 1807 January 21; No. 2377
- Henry Knox to John Jay, 1781 October 21; No. 2378
- Henry Knox to Samuel Pike, 1783 October 28; No. 2379
- Henry Knox to Joseph Howell, Jr., 1791 November 9; No. 2380
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to Robert Lawson, 1781 July 30; No. 2381
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to "mon cher general", 1809 August 6; No. 2382
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to William H. Crawford, 1820 July 20; No. 2383
- Armand-Charles Tuffin, marquis de La Rouerie to Henry "Lorance" Laurens, 1778 October; No. 2384
- Tobias Lear to Robert Brent, 1815 May 15; No. 2385
- Charles Lee to the President of the Provincial Council of North Carolina (Cornelius Harnett), 1776 June 29; No. 2386
- Henry Lee to Samuel Blachley Webb, 1786 April 6; No. 2387
- Benjamin Lincoln to George Clinton, 1787 February 14; No. 2388
- Otto Christian Wilhelm von Linsing, 1778 March 15; No. 2389
- Benson J. Lossing, 1858 February; No. 2390
- John Campbell, Lord Loudouin to William Wildman, 1777 March 12; No. 2391
- Louis XVI, King of France, 1784 June 4; No. 2392
- James Madison to Tench Coxe, 1817 March 11; No. 2393
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Governor (John Hancock) to Ebenezer Hancock, 1789 March 18; No. 2394
- William Maxwell to William Alexander, Lord Stirling, 1779 January 30; No. 2395
- James Monroe to ________, 1798 May 14; No. 2396
- Andrew Moodie, 1778 January 1-May 31; No. 2397
- Robert Morris, by order of the Secret Committee of the Continental Congress to Thomas Mumford, 1776 August 22; No. 2398
- Robert Morris to James and Adam Hunter, 1777 December 27; No. 2399
- Robert Morris to John Nicholson, 1794 November 21; No. 2400
- Elizabeth Morrison to John Morrison, 1777 September 13; No. 2401
- William North, 1777 August 9; No. 2402
- Thomas Paine to Thomas Fitzsimmons, 1786 May 19; No. 2403
- James Parton, 1889?; No. 2404
- Thomas Penn to Sir William Johnson, 1768 November 2; No. 2405
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor (Thomas Mifflin) to Persifor Frazer, 1791 August 17; No. 2406
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor (Thomas Mifflin), 1802 March 24; No. 2407
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Executive Council (Joseph Reed, president) to all concerned, 1779 November 23; No. 2408
- Pennsylvania, Philadelphia and Vicinity, 1777-1778; No. 2409; 1.0 vol.
- Sir William Pepperell, 1758 August 29; No. 2410
- Timothy Pickering to Samuel W. Dana, 1812 January 23; No. 2411
- Joseph Reed to Nathanael Greene, 1778 November 5; No. 2412
- Paul Revere, n.d.; No. 2413
- John Rice to Benjamin Franklin, 1787 August; No. 2414
- Benjamin? Runwa to Aaron Burr, 1778 August 18; No. 2415
- Philip Schuyler to Samuel Jones and Thomas Tillotson, 1797 March 4; No. 2416
- Province of South Carolina to the sheriffs, 1774 July 5; No. 2417
- Province of South Carolina, Court to the sheriffs, 1772 October 14; No. 2418
- State of South Carolina, Court to the sheriffs, 1788 March 18; No. 2419
- Benjamin Stoddert to William Lyles, 1784 May 20; No. 2420
- John Sullivan to Benjamin Stelle, 1778 December 21; No. 2421
- James Smith Symes to the President of the Pennsylvania Committee of Safety (Benjamin Franklin), 1775 October 30; No. 2422
- Hugh Tallant to Joseph Tallant, 1774 October 3; No. 2423
- Samuel Tolbert, John Willson, and others to Richard Humpton, 1783 February 23; No. 2424
- John Trumbull to Thomas McEuen, Thomas Hale, and William Davidson, 1804 September 11; No. 2425
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jabez Huntington, 1777 July 11; No. 2426
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jabez Huntington, 1777 November 7; No. 2427
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President), 1777 July 31; No. 2428
- United States, District of Boston and Charlestown, 1824 November 10; No. 2429
- United States, President (Andrew Jackson) to John B. Seward, 1831 March 7; No. 2430
- United States, President (George Washington) to James Murray, 1796 September 17; No. 2431
- Richard Varick to Daniel Phenix, 1793 July 22; No. 2432
- Louis-Pierre, marquis de Vienne to George Washington, 1778 September 15; No. 2433
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (Patrick Henry) to James Taylor, 1785 January 10; No. 2434
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (Patrick Henry), 1786 January 12; No. 2435
- James Warren to Elbridge Gerry, 1785 July 28; No. 2436
- Joseph Warren, by order of the Massachusetts Provincial Congress to Benjamin Franklin, 1775 April 26; No. 2437
- George Washington, 1768; No. 2438
- George Washington to John Harper, 1775 February 18; No. 2439
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1776 June 24; No. 2440
- George Washington to Dr. Benjamin Rush, 1777 May 16; No. 2441
- George Washington to William Alexander, Lord Stirling, 1777 July 30; No. 2442
- George Washington to John Burgoyne, 1778 March 11; No. 2443
- George Washington to Daniel Morgan, 1778 December 7; No. 2444
- George Washington to Arthur St. Clair, 1779 June 2; No. 2445
- George Washington to Henry Lee, 1779 September 30; No. 2446
- George Washington to Benjamin Tallmadge, 1780 May 19; No. 2447
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1780 May 28; No. 2448
- George Washington to Arthur St. Clair, 1780 June 22; No. 2449
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1780 June 27; No. 2450
- George Washington to Henry Lee, 1780 July 24; No. 2451
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1780 December 26; No. 2452
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1781 February 24; No. 2453
- George Washington to John Dickinson, 1781 December 19; No. 2454
- George Washington to William Stephens Smith, 1783 June 20; No. 2455
- George Washington to Friedrich Adolph, baron von Riedesel, 1783 July 14; No. 2456
- George Washington to Richard Varick, 1783 October 2; No. 2457
- George Washington to Sir Edward Newenham, 1785 March 20; No. 2458
- George Washington to Dr. Thomas Ruston, 1788 August 31; No. 2459
- George Washington to Thomas Bee, 1789 May 5; No. 2460
- George Washington to the Secretaries of State, Treasury, and War (Thomas Jefferson, Alexander Hamilton, and Henry Knox), No. 2461
- George Washington to Charles Cotesworth Pinckney, 1796 July 8; No. 2462
- George Washington to James Anderson, 1799 September 16; No. 2463
- Martha Dandridge Custis Washington to "Fanny" Francis Bassett Washington, 1794 May 25; No. 2464
- Anthony Wayne to William Preston, 1796 February 13; No. 2465
- Otho Holland Williams to Robert Purviance, 1785 September 26; No. 2466
- Oliver Wolcott, Jr. to Otho Holland Williams, 1792 November 22; No. 2467
- David Wooster to Messrs. Darting and Whiting, 1753 April 17; No. 2468
- John Plasgrave Wyllys to Ebenezer Huntington, 1781 March 29; No. 2469
- John Andre to Dr. John McNamara Hayes, 1779 June 30; No. 2470
- Moore Furman to Clement Biddle, 1778 August 20; No. 2471
- Moore Furman to Clement Biddle, 1778 August 26; No. 2472
- General Washington's letter, declaring his acceptance of the command of the armies of the United States, 1798 July 18; No. 2473
- Timothy Hurst, agent for Thomas Ingram, Sir John Bridger, Lady Rebecca Bridger, and Mary Eliot, heirs of John Bollers to the President (Benjamin Franklin) and Supreme Executive Council of Pennsylvania, 1787 March 2; No. 2474
- John Jay to Henry White, 1783 December 30; No. 2475
- John Jay to Henry White, 1785 June 3; No. 2476
- Marquis of Lambertye, "Chamberlain of the King of Poland" to ________, 1755 July 3; No. 2477
- Henry Brockholst Livingston to Isaac Gouverneur, 1776 January 28; No. 2478
- Pennsylvania, City of Philadelphia, n.d.; No. 2479
- Colony of Pennsylvania to Thomas Holme, 1684 October 9; No. 2480
- State of Pennsylvania, Assembly to the Supreme Executive Council, 1781 December 15; No. 2481
- Augustus Van Cortlandt to Henry White, 1785 March 10; No. 2482